{"success": 1, "total": 10, "result": [{"ID": "55fa6a71e4b043d0caf2726a", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "\u4ee5\u4e0a\u90fd\u4e0d\u5bf9", "optionC": "\u65e0\u9650", "optionAnswer": "A", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "1", "type": "1", "optionA": "0", "knowledge": "C/C++", "question": "\u4e0b\u5217for\u5faa\u73af\u7684\u5faa\u73af\u4f53\u6267\u884c\u6b21\u6570\u4e3afor(int i=10, j=1; i=j=0; i++, j--)", "title": "Xunlei-2014C++\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377B"}, {"ID": "55fa6a71e4b043d0caf2726b", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "\u51fa\u9519", "optionC": "xy123ABC", "optionAnswer": "D", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "z123ABC", "type": "1", "optionA": "xyz123ABC", "knowledge": "C/C++", "question": "\u4e0b\u9762\u7a0b\u5e8f\u7684\u8f93\u51fa\u7ed3\u679c\u662fchar *p1= \u201c123\u201d, *p2 = \u201cABC\u201d, str\uff3b50\uff3d= \"xyz\";\nstrcpy\uff08str+2,strcat\uff08p1,p2\uff09\uff09;\ncout << str;", "title": "Xunlei-2014C++\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377B"}, {"ID": "55fa6a71e4b043d0caf2726c", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "6, 6, 4", "optionC": "6, 4, 4", "optionAnswer": "B", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "7, 4, 4", "type": "1", "optionA": "4, 4, 4", "knowledge": "C/C++", "question": "\u4e0b\u9762\u51fd\u6570\u7684\u6267\u884c\u7ed3\u679c\u662f\u8f93\u51fachar str[ ] = \u201cxunlei\u201d;\nchar *p = str;\nint n = 10;\nprintf(\u201c%d, %d, %d/n\u201d, sizeof(str), sizeof(p), sizeof(n));", "title": "Xunlei-2014C++\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377B"}, {"ID": "55fa6a71e4b043d0caf2726d", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "16", "optionC": "13", "optionAnswer": "D", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "12", "type": "1", "optionA": "11", "knowledge": "C/C++/\u64cd\u4f5c\u7cfb\u7edf", "question": "\u73b0\u5728\u6709\u4ee5\u4e0b\u8bed\u53e5\uff1astruct _THUNDER{\n       int iVersion;\n       char cTag;\n       char cAdv;\n       int iUser;\n       char cEnd;\n}Thunder;\nint sz = sizeof(Thunder);\u5219\u6267\u884c\u540e\uff0c\u53d8\u91cfsz\u7684\u503c\u5c06\u5f97\u5230\n", "title": "Xunlei-2014C++\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377B"}, {"ID": "55fa6a71e4b043d0caf2726e", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "\u7a0b\u5e8f\u5d29\u6e83", "optionC": "Thunderownloader", "optionAnswer": "D", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "under Downloader", "type": "1", "optionA": "Thunder Downloader", "knowledge": "C/C++/\u64cd\u4f5c\u7cfb\u7edf", "question": "\u6709\u5982\u4e0b\u7a0b\u5e8f\u6bb5\uff1avoid GetMemeory(char* p)\n{\n    p = (char*) malloc (100);\n\uff5d\nvoid test()\n{\n    char *str=NULL;\n    GetMemory(str);\n    strcpy(str,\u201dThunder\u201d);\n    strcat(str+2, \u201cDownloader\u201d);\n    printf(str);\n}\u8bf7\u95ee\u8fd0\u884cTest\u51fd\u6570\u7ed3\u679c\u662f\uff1a", "title": "Xunlei-2014C++\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377B"}, {"ID": "55fa6a71e4b043d0caf2726f", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "*s.p = 5", "optionC": "s.*p = 5", "optionAnswer": "D", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "s->p = 5", "type": "1", "optionA": "s.p = 5", "knowledge": "C/C++", "question": "p\u662f\u6307\u5411\u7c7bX\u7684\u6210\u5458m\u7684\u6307\u9488\uff0cs\u662f\u7c7bX\u7684\u4e00\u4e2a\u5bf9\u8c61\u3002\u73b0\u8981\u7ed9m\u8d4b\u503c\uff0c\uff08\uff09\u662f\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u3002", "title": "Xunlei-2014C++\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377B"}, {"ID": "55fa6a71e4b043d0caf27270", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "\u884c\u53c2p\u81ea\u8eab\u7684\u5730\u5740\u503c", "optionC": "\u4e00\u4e2a\u4e34\u65f6\u5b58\u50a8\u5355\u5143\u7684\u5730\u5740", "optionAnswer": "B", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "\u884c\u53c2p\u4e2d\u5b58\u653e\u7684\u5730\u5740\u503c", "type": "1", "optionA": "\u65e0\u786e\u5207\u503c", "knowledge": "C/C++", "question": "\u51fd\u6570fun\uff08char* p\uff09 {\n    return p;\n}\n\u7684\u8fd4\u56de\u503c\u662f", "title": "Xunlei-2014C++\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377B"}, {"ID": "55fa6a71e4b043d0caf27271", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "a/b*b == a", "optionC": "a/b*b + a%b == a", "optionAnswer": "C", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "a/b*b/a == 1", "type": "1", "optionA": "a*b/a*b == 1", "knowledge": "\u7f16\u7a0b\u57fa\u7840", "question": "a,b\u5747\u4e3a\u4e0d\u7b49\u4e8e0\u7684\u6574\u5f62\u53d8\u91cf\uff0c\u4ee5\u4e0b\u5173\u7cfb\u5f0f\u6052\u6210\u7acb\u7684\u662f\uff1a", "title": "Xunlei-2014C++\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377B"}, {"ID": "55fa6a71e4b043d0caf27272", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "NEW\u662f\u4e00\u4e2a\u7ed3\u6784\u4f53\u53d8\u91cf", "optionC": "NEW\u662f\u4e00\u4e2a\u7ed3\u6784\u4f53\u7c7b\u578b", "optionAnswer": "C", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "ST\u662f\u4e00\u4e2a\u7ed3\u6784\u4f53\u7c7b\u578b", "type": "1", "optionA": "\u4ee5\u4e0a\u7684\u8bf4\u660e\u5f62\u5f0f\u975e\u6cd5", "knowledge": "C/C++", "question": "\u8bbe\u6709\u5982\u4e0b\u8bf4\u660e\uff1atypedef struct ST{\n    long a; int b; char c[2];\n} NEW;\n\u5219\u4e0b\u9762\u53d9\u8ff0\u4e2d\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff1a", "title": "Xunlei-2014C++\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377B"}, {"ID": "55fa6a71e4b043d0caf27273", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "\u4f7f\u7528\u5185\u8054\u51fd\u6570\u7684\u5730\u65b9\u4f1a\u5728\u8fd0\u884c\u9636\u6bb5\u7528\u5185\u8054\u51fd\u6570\u4f53\u66ff\u6362\u6389", "optionC": "\u7c7b\u7684\u4fdd\u62a4\u6210\u5458\u51fd\u6570\u4e0d\u80fd\u4f5c\u4e3a\u5185\u8054\u51fd\u6570", "optionAnswer": "B", "answer": "  ", "optionB": "\u5728\u6240\u6709\u7c7b\u8bf4\u660e\u4e2d\u5185\u90e8\u5b9a\u4e49\u7684\u6210\u5458\u51fd\u6570\u90fd\u662f\u5185\u8054\u51fd\u6570", "type": "1", "optionA": "\u7c7b\u7684\u79c1\u6709\u6210\u5458\u51fd\u6570\u4e0d\u80fd\u4f5c\u4e3a\u5185\u8054\u51fd\u6570", "knowledge": "C/C++", "question": "\u5173\u4e8e\u5185\u8054\u51fd\u6570\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08\uff09", "title": "Xunlei-2014C++\u7b14\u8bd5\u5377B"}]}